<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="title_activity_about_chip">About CHIP</string>
    <string name="about_welcome_title">Welcome to CHIP!</string>
    <string name="about_welcome_text">Our Community Health Innovator Program or "CHIP" is a novel framework that facilitates local innovation to improve health behaviors. CHIP empowers communities to identify health challenges for families with infants and young children, and address these challenges through innovative local ("on-the-ground") and global ("adaptable") solutions. Homegrown health promotion has the most positive outcomes. When health challenges are identified locally, and communities obtain the support to create innovative solutions, community residents are more likely to embrace the "nudge", "disrupt" negative health behaviors, "leapfrog" development, and "reach" beyond to the next stage. Therefore, promoting local innovations that provide low-cost health and social benefits to marginalized and vulnerable communities is central to the future of global health. However, in low-income countries, innovators frequently lack access to low-cost training, adequate technologies, funding initiatives, and multi-sectoral networks who are interested in facilitating and adopting social innovations. Current social innovation frameworks and incubators have varied outcomes, but often lack all the required inputs for success. The CHIP framework was designed to address current limitations and its structure evolved through a collaborative effort between the Program Team and an International Advisory Board (IAB), composed of practitioners, academics, and community members from Detroit, Haiti, Ghana and Nepal. The IAB identified CHIP as an approach, which is needed, feasible, and can be integrated within local infrastructures.</string>
    <string name="about_welcome_textP1">Our Community Health Innovator Program or "CHIP" is a novel framework that facilitates local innovation to improve health behaviors. CHIP empowers communities to identify health challenges for families with infants and young children, and address these challenges through innovative local ("on-the-ground") and global ("adaptable") solutions.</string>
    <string name="about_welcome_textP2">Homegrown health promotion has the most positive outcomes. When health challenges are identified locally, and communities obtain the support to create innovative solutions, community residents are more likely to embrace the "nudge", "disrupt" negative health behaviors, "leapfrog" development, and "reach" beyond to the next stage. Therefore, promoting local innovations that provide low-cost health and social benefits to marginalized and vulnerable communities is central to the future of global health. However, in low-income countries, innovators frequently lack access to low-cost training, adequate technologies, funding initiatives, and multi-sectoral networks who are interested in facilitating and adopting social innovations.</string>
    <string name="about_welcome_textP3">Current social innovation frameworks and incubators have varied outcomes, but often lack all the required inputs for success. The CHIP framework was designed to address current limitations and its structure evolved through a collaborative effort between the Program Team and an International Advisory Board (IAB), composed of practitioners, academics, and community members from Detroit, Haiti, Ghana and Nepal. The IAB identified CHIP as an approach, which is needed, feasible, and can be integrated within local infrastructures.</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_title">Contributors to this project:</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_list1">Henry Ford Health System</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_list2">Wayne State University</string>
    <string name="about_contributors_list3">Graduate Students from the School of Business, MSITM Program, Oakland University</string>
</resources>